artipoppe.com 2016-04-04

# Privacy - Artipoppe - Avant-garde babywearing design house Artipoppe – Avant-garde babywearing design house

## Privacy

Through its website, www.artipoppe.com, Artipoppe will process privacy-sensitive or personal data. Artipoppe values the privacy of its customers and observes due care in processing and protecting personal data.  
Artipoppe processes data in compliance with the requirements laid down by the Dutch Personal Data Protection Act (DPDA). Artipoppe does not outsource any of its data processing. In this privacy statement, Artipoppe will explain which personal data is collected and for which purposes. It is recommended that you read it carefully.  
This privacy statement was last amended on February 17 2015.  
Use of personal data:  
Artipoppe only retains personal data that is provided directly by you or for which it is clear that it has been supplied to us to be processed.

Artipoppe uses the following data to process orders:  
– Name and address  
– E-mail address / Paypal address  
Registration  
www.artipoppe.com offers the possibility to register your name and email address. Artipoppe will retain this data and eventually use it for:  
– managing subscriptions to newsletters,  
– sending information about the company and it’s activities as well as, subject to your consent, publicity or marketing information.  
In the event of suspicion of fraud or misuse of our website Artipoppe may hand over personal data to the entitled authorities.  
Providing data to third parties  
We will not provide your data to third parties, unless it is necessary for the execution of the agreement you concluded with us or if this is required by law.  
Our website features social media buttons. These buttons are used by the providers of these services to collect your personal data.  
Security  
We take security measures to reduce misuse of and unauthorised access to personal data. We do keep statistics on our website, but these are kept anonymous at all times.  
Third-party websites  
This statement is not applicable to third-party websites connected to this website through links. We cannot guarantee that these third parties will handle your personal data in a secure and careful manner. We recommend you read these websites’ privacy statements before making use of these websites.  
Changes to this privacy statement  
We reserve the right to modify this statement. We recommend that you review this statement regularly, so that you remain informed of any changes.  
Inspection and modification of your data  
You can always contact us at info@artipoppe.com if you have any questions regarding our privacy policy or wish to review, modify or delete your personal data.
